mustanglist.com 2009-11-07

# Privacy Policy .: MustangList.com Knowledge Base

At Mustang List, we respect and protect the privacy of our customers and those who use our websites. The following Privacy Statement provides details about how your personal information is collected and used. This privacy statement applies to the network of Mustang List websites, products and services that are located in, but not limited to the Mustang List domain.

Information Collection and Use  
Mustang List is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Mustang List collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

Our websites offers several opportunities for visitors to register for promotional and informational mailings, online webinars and resources, and for assistance in evaluating our software and services. These registration forms are often linked to Mustang List's mailing lists and require users to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this contact information to send users information about our company and its products and services if requested or necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time (see the choice/opt-out section below).

Sharing and Usage  
We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information with third parties for their promotional use. Occasionally, we enter into contracts with third parties so that they can assist us in servicing you (for example, providing customer service). The contracts prohibit them from using any of your personal information for their own purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information we provide to them. We may also disclose information to partners who introduced you to Mustang List's services in order to ensure they are properly compensated for their efforts. Lastly, we may disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required under the law. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities, to comply with a legal process such as court order, subpoena, search warrant, or law enforcement request.

Use of Web Technologies  
We use a variety of technologies on our sites. Among these are cookies; a piece of information that our websites provide to your browser when you visit our sites. Cookies allow us to verify the login status of customers using products or services linked directly with our website, track point of entry to point of registration for those users participating in our affiliate signup programs, and to track and measure the success of a particular marketing campaign. Cookies also allow us to track overall site usage and determine areas users prefer, enabling us to make your visit to our websites easier by recognizing you when you return and helping to provide you with a customized experience. If you choose to disable cookies, you may be unable to us our our websites.

We may access and set cookies using web beacons. These web beacons provide us useful information regarding our site such as which pages users access. When we send you emails, we may include a web beacon or other methods to allow us to determine the number of people who open our emails. When you click on a link in an email, we record this individual response to allow us to customize our (and our partner's) offerings to you.

We also use graphics, pixels, and / or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These files enable us to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with us. 

We also keep track of activity on our website via log files stored on our web servers. We collect information such as IP address, browser type and version, and pages you view. We also keep track of how you got to our site and any links you click on to leave our site. We use your website activity to assist us in offering you a personalized Web experience, assist you with technical support, diagnose problems with our server, administer our websites and to tailor our product and service offerings to you.

Links  
Some of our sites provide links to third-party websites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers. While on these sites, Mustang List or its partners may collect information about you. Because Mustang List does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personally identifiable information.

Security  
We take every precaution to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information by using industry-recognized security safeguards such as firewalls, coupled with carefully developed security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration. When we ask for sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, we protect it through the use of encryption during transmission, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Mustang List takes care to reinforce the importance of our website visitors' security and privacy among our employees. Our employees are trained and required to safeguard your information and, using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, we restrict access to personal information to those employees and agents for business purposes only. Additionally, we use internal and external resources to review the adequacy of our security procedures.

Choice/Opt-out  
Mustang List provides users the opportunity to opt-in, opt-out or change preferences via a link in the footer of most email messages. These options are made available when you sign-up for our email lists and in email messages delivered from our company. 

Some communications (e.g. important account notifications and billing information) are necessary for all Mustang List customers. You must cancel your Mustang List account to unsubscribe from these communications. To cancel your Mustang List account, please email us at [support@mustanglist.com](mailto:support@mustanglist.com).

Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the Mustang List Website. So our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
